Don't worry.
We didn't come here to interfere or anything.
You might say we're here to assist.
Wait, to assist?
That's right.
If we get the top score on the quiz and obtain the final card,
we'll sell it to you for 2.5 billion.
That's just 5% of your total reward.
A pretty reasonable price, don't you think?
Oh yeah, they don't know about Batera yet.
Works for us, if you guys win.
Is that why they're all here, for the chance to sell us the last card?
With the game coming close to the end,
they're probably hoping to get some share of the reward money for themselves.
And it looks to me like they're all planning to take the quiz in teams.
So, what should we do?
Well, I think that we ought to do it by ourselves.
Yeah, and whoever gets the lowest scores gets punished.
Okay, I'm in.
Honestly, they've got guts.
They just finished a life-or-death battle,
and now they're facing the final event with such confidence.
I'm willing to bet that those two enjoyed this game more than anyone else.
Best of luck, boys.
We'll be right back.
I caught the bomber.
Number 84, the Paladin's Necklace, is offered as a prize in which monthly tournament?
Yes!
Okay.
Now for the final question.
What is the name of card number zero?
A. Ruler's Banquet.
B. Ruler's Invitation.
C. Ruler's Welcome.
What was it?
The quiz is over.
I will now announce the player who received the top score.
With a total of 87 out of 100 points, the winning player is gone.
Huh?
We have all 100 cards!
You did it!
I hate to say it, but congrats, you deserve it.
Thanks a lot!
That means Killua's gonna get punished!
Damn!
I wonder how many total points I've got.
Ruler's Invitation?
It looks like only the one with the badge is invited.
So, I guess Lymeiro is the capital?
And do I have to go there all by myself?
We'll wait for you outside the castle.
Hey, you really got it, huh?
That kid collected all the cards.
Okay, then.
Let's have a contest.
Winner gets all your cards.
Sorry, but you don't have a choice.
Then, I'll take an Accompany card.
Wait, that won't work.
Not one of us have been to Li-Meiro before.
We should use Drift,
since we've never visited the other cities before.
In that case, I'll use Drift to go to Li-Meiro,
then come back here for you guys.
And Accompany should work after that.
Drift on!
Oh, bingo!
Go, let's go!
Yeah!
Accompany on!
Li-Meiro!
Those kids are really amazing.
They actually beat the Bellum Brothers.
Well, yeah, of course they did.
They beat the Bombers, didn't they?
It's true.
Those boys are considerably stronger now
than they were when I first encountered them.
Even so,
they're still weaker than Genthru and Raw Power.
Their strategy must have been flawless.
Well, no matter.
I'll let you have the reward for clearing the game.
Magnetic force on.
Krullo Lucilfer.
I'll be heading back to the real world now
to make a fortune on an exorcism.
I wonder what he's feeling.
What do you mean?
I mean, he might actually meet Jean, right?
The father he's been searching for all this time.
Hmm.
Welcome, sir, to Greed Island Castle.
This way.
Whoa, what a dump.
I've brought Gon, the top scorer.
Huh?
Oh, hey, I've been waiting for you, kid.
So, I hear you're Jin's son, right?
Well, go ahead and take a seat, huh?
Okay, but where do you want me to sit?
What, there's no space over there?
Then just make some.
Like this.
Oh, how long is that over there?
Ah, where did I put it?
Aha, here it is.
Huh?
There you go.
Ruler's blessing, the reward for whoever gets the top score.
How about it, isn't it the coolest?
I bet you're surprised.
Are you surprised?
There are about 10,000 people in the city,
so there's a real good chance that one of them is.
Wait, did I get your hopes up?
Did I?
Well, or maybe you were thinking your dad, Gene,
could be the ruler, huh?
I didn't think that.
I never even thought that he would be here on the island.
Oh, is that so?
That's good then.
You know, cause he's not.
Mr. Doom.
Hmm?
Can we please move on now?
Yeah, sure.
That's my bad.
Listen up.
So you've actually collected all 100 cards that Greed Island has to offer.
Well done.
That milestone triggers a new event.
Let me see.
Ah, here it is.
There.
Now open it up.
This case has slots where you can place three specified slot cards.
But that's not all.
You can take all three of them back with you to use in the real world.
However, just so you know, you can't take multiple copies of the same card.
You have to choose from one of the specified slot cards there in your binder,
but you can pick any three you like.
Hmm.
Okay.
You've reached the end of the game, so you get to make a choice.
You want the normal generic ending, or the one that's just for you.
There's one for me?
Yep, that's right.
What'll it be?
Hmm.
I'll take the generic one.
Oh, yeah?
Why that one?
Well, I didn't clear the game all by myself.
And if it's generic, my friends can watch too, right?
Oh, okay.
I see, I see.
Mr. Dune.
Huh?
Would you please stop teasing our guest already?
I'm sorry, but there's no such thing as an ending tailor just for you.
There isn't?
Afraid not.
But we were given permission to tell you a few things after you'd beaten the game.
Huh?
How rude of us.
We'll introduce ourselves.
My name is List.
This is Dune.
And as you probably know by now, both of us are friends with your old man.
This game was created by Gene, along with ten of his friends.
The name Greed Island was only decided upon because it incorporates the first letter of each of their names.
Your father was in charge, so we wanted to select a word that began with G.
And it wasn't long before we settled on Greed.
Have you met Razor yet?
Well, he's the R, and I'm the L.
The woman who explains the game at the beginning is the twin of the woman you see when leaving the island, Ita and Elena.
Both of their names start with E.
See that?
And then we've got the letter D.
You wanna hear it?
Wanna hear my story?
Well?
Yeah, okay.
Then pay attention.
Here's the thing.
Your father, Gene, is...
Your dad...
It's a huge jerk!
A huge jerk!
My name is Dune, you got that?
And what do you think the first letter is?
Uh...
Isn't it D?
I can't believe it!
You too, huh?
Makes sense, I guess.
I mean, you are Gene's son.
I thought we were talking about the letter D.
It's W, okay?
Spells Dune!
And that was my name!
But even my oldest friends in the world thought it started with a D.
How do you like that?
So when we all decided on the name of the game, I was perfectly clear.
My name starts with a W, and that's final.
But what do you think Gene said when I told him that, huh?
Really?
Then just ditch the W.
Starting now, your name is D-W-U-N.
Okay, Dune?
Isn't that unbelievable!
He went and changed my name without even asking me about it first,
just so he didn't have to change the title of this stupid game.
What's even more amazing is that only a minute later,
Gene already had Dune's name legally changed.
And all he needed was a phone and a computer.
Worse than that, he took the E off the end because, get this,
he thought it was too confusing.
But your luck has gotten much better as a result, hasn't it?
Well, I guess so.
I've never been healthier and I've been eating...
Oh yeah!
Actually I've never been 8X7 years old.
With every day, he would've added up to life.
You can get to walk a mountain, and I'll see how he punished AND
LA JANES 127 year old!
Once I pick the three cards I want to keep, they say I'm supposed to go to the harbor.
So what about your father? Did they tell you anything?
Yeah, but they couldn't tell me where he is right now because they don't know.
I see. Then I guess the game didn't have any clues for you after all.
Well, no surprise since that's what his message said to begin with.
Yeah, that's true.
So, let's get back to the three cards. Which ones will you take?
How about we each pick one and then go from there?
I know my pick, Blue Planet! This is still the one I want!
I can't wait to hold you snuggly in my arms.
Which one do you want to pick, Killua?
I'm still thinking. Have you got one yet, Gon?
Mm-hmm. I think so anyway.
Really? Which one?
Hold on, let me see. This one.
Which one?
Huh? Wait, why would you choose this one?
Hey, I get it. That does make sense. You are only allowed to take specified slot cards.
Yeah. Sounds fun.
So, when did you think of it?
Um, as soon as I saw it, actually.
But, this one's not going to be enough.
Right. We'll need this one, too.
What?
I think it'll work. Do you?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah. And this is the only way to pull it off.
Wait, what's the only way? What are you two talking about?
You get the Blue Planet. You okay with that?
Tell me what you're talking about right now!
Congratulations on clearing the game.
And now, choose three specified slot cards from your binder. Any three that you desire.
You've chosen number two, Strip of Beach.
Number 81, Blue Planet.
And number 84, Paladin's Necklace.
Are you positive that these are the three cards you want?
Yep!
All right. I will now return your ring. Very nice work.
Thanks a whole lot, Miss... uh... Miss Elena?
So you remembered my name. Thank you for that.
Goodbye now.
Welcome back.
Thanks.
What do you think? Are we back in the real world now, or what?
I can't tell.
Well, the game was part of the real world, remember?
Hurry up and get your binder out! Let's get this party started!
Book!
Dane!
Yay! This is it!
This is the one that I really wanted!
I've been dreaming about you for so long!
I've never been happier!
Now, what should I name it?
Bluey!
Or maybe Planet Eve!
Planet?
Oh, yes, yes! That's the one!
So, what about the ones you two picked? Happy with your decision?
Yeah. We chose the best ones, right?
Oh.
Well, should we do it?
Yeah!
And game!
Killua, I'll take it.
Yes! It really worked!
It sure did.
Oh, now I get it.
So, you just used Transform to turn a company into a specified slot card, and then you used the Paladin's necklace to revert it!
That was some clever thinking, you guys, but I have to say, I'm surprised you would go to all that trouble for an accompany instead of choosing another specified slot card.
Yeah. It's just, if I hadn't been the first to enter the game, then I wouldn't have noticed. So I guess it was a good thing that I was.
Huh?
Do you remember when we played Rock, Paper, Scissors?
You mean John Ken?
Yeah.
See, I was the first person to enter the game.
And while I was standing there waiting for Killua, there was nobody else around.
That means the first person I met in the game should have been the second to show up, Mr. Gorenu.
But he wasn't. When I checked my binder, it said that there was somebody I'd met before him.
Jean is spelled G-I-N-G.
Oh, I see. So Neeg is an anagram.
My guess is that when I was just a baby, I must have come here with Jean.
Maybe this was his way of trying to tell me.
If I'm ready to give up everything I have and go find him,
then I have to get strong enough to clear the game.
You really are tenacious. It's impressive.
Well, what are you planning to do once you find Jean?
Jean, that's easy. I'll introduce him to Killua.
Huh?
I'll tell him he's my best friend in the world.
You what?
Shut up.
That's embarrassing, man.
Really?
Huh?
Oh, stop.
I can't take it.
It must be my age, but it's so easy to make me cry.
Oh, hey. Why don't you come with us to see Jean, Biscuit?
Thank you, but I think I'll pass.
I'm not interested in men with kids.
Okay.
If I stay much longer, I'll get too attached to them. Like a parent.
I guess that's it then. Take care, Biscuit.
I will. You boys too, okay?
Thanks so much for everything.
Us!
A company on!
Neg!
Bye, boys.
Goon has cleared the game that his father created, becoming much stronger in the process.
Is the one waiting before him really Jean, or is it someone else?
Bye, boys.
Thank you.
We shall take care.
and
you
Asa hii ni
Te la sa reta kizu
Wa lai wa te
Owaru hoto nai
Tabi wo
Tuzuzukeyou
Mukai kaze to
Shite i na ga ra
Soreでも susumu
Li yu ga alu
Takara tomo yo
Oite iku
Tame dakya ni
Ikiru no waまだ
Hai ai ai daro
Mi ni tsuketa mono
Takai konda mono
Te ba na shita toki
Hajimaru na ni ka
Umaku ikiteku
Recipi wo
Yaburi sute te kanjiu
Rezum
So bokra no yari ka pa de
Coming up! The Great Island Tutorial!
Kbyap off
Enwes
Dilipo
sought
Entry
La
Not